pointsincase.com 2006-06-18

# Privacy Policy :: Points in Case.com

**Terms of Service**

We at Pointsincase.com ("Website") agree to provide you with information and other computer services subject to the Terms of Service outlined below. You agree to use our service in accordance with these Terms. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change these Terms of Service from time to time, in which case we will post the revised terms at this location. By continuing to use our services after we post any such changes, you accept the Terms of Service, as modified. 

1\. Visitor Information Collected  
2\. Public Feedback  
3\. Site Contact  
4\. Submissions and Licensing  
5\. Advertisements and Third Parties  

* * *

**Visitor Information Collected**

Our Website uses cookies, but they are not used to store personal information about users, they will not be shared with anyone else, and they will not be used to contact you.

The major evidence of your visit is in the form of an access log, a text file that records certain facts about your visit, such as what page you looked at, what kind of browser you were using, and in some cases what page you came from to get here. This is standard information provided by your browser and it is collected by nearly every website out there, even the Pope's. This information does NOT contain your address, your credit card number, the number of children you have, or any similar personal information. Data collected is used to determine things like, "IP address 92.734.531 visited quotes.htm at 8:34PM and viewed 10 pages on Pointsincase.com."

We use these Website logs to improve the value of our Website, such as personalizing and customizing your experience on our Website. This information will be treated with the same sensitivity as personal information you give us and will not be shared (except at the aggregate level) with any third parties. In the rare case of Website abuse, we may use web log data to personally identify users and report them to the appropriate authorities.

We sometimes ask for a name and e-mail address. We do not share your e-mail address with anyone. We don't use it ourselves, except to alert winners or tell people about problems. We generally announce winners by name, though, and we may display all entries with names, so if that makes you uncomfortable, use a pseudonym.

We do maintain weekly mailing lists which we use to send out exclusive Website content. We never add people to this unless they explicitly tell us to (i.e. sign up online).

* * *

**Public Feedback**

Personal information collected through our public feedback system on columns and articles is not shared with anyone else, nor is it used in any way other than to be displayed with your post. Our feedback system IS moderated however. We reserve the right to edit and/or delete comments at any time. This is usually done only when we feel a particular posting is especially vulgar, hateful, or otherwise inappropriate. Please, keep it civil, it's only a humor site.  

* * *

**Site Contact**

If you use any instant messaging system to send instant messages (IM's) to the AOL Instant Messenger screenname "courtjester5000," you agree to have the entirety of your messages published **_with your screenname_**. If you are under 13 years of age, or do not wish your instant messages to be published, please do not send messages at all.  We reserve the right to edit IM's for brevity, clarity, grammar and spelling.

If you send e-mail to any "@pointsincase.com" email address, we assume you are permitting your email and/or attachments to be published with your name and your email address. We reserve the right to edit emails and attachments for brevity, clarity, or grammar and spelling. All submissions become copyright of HotIron Media.

* * *

**Submissions and Licensing** When you post public feedback, upload a file, submit content via our submission forms, submit content by email to any "@pointsincase.com" address, or otherwise provide us with material for display on the Website, you are granting to HotIron Media and Pointsincase.com a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to: 

**1.** Use, copy, sublicense, adapt, transmit, publicly perform or display any such communication. 

**2.** Sublicense to third parties the unrestricted right to exercise any of the foregoing rights granted with respect to the communication. The foregoing grants shall include the right to exploit any proprietary rights in such communication, including but not limited to rights under copyright, trademark, service mark or patent laws under any relevant jurisdiction.

* * *

**Advertisements and Third Parties**

Our advertisements are sometimes served by outside agencies (third parties). Even though you are looking at our pages, you are looking at their images or links, and they collect their own logs and may serve their own cookies. They have their own privacy policies which you may want to review. Please [ask us](http://www.pointsincase.com/about.htm#contact) if you would like to review their privacy policies.

We may choose to run ads from other networks with no notice. Keep in mind that any site you go to as a result of clicking on an advertisement banner or link will have its own separate privacy policy or lack of same.
